http://www.europeanparking.eu/en/imprint-privacy-disclaimer/

Imprint & Privacy & Disclaimer
Imprint
European Parking Association e.V.Richartzstraße 10D- 50667 KölnPhone:+ 49 221 / 2571016Telefax:+ 49 221 / 2571019E-Mail: epa(at)europeanaparking.euCourt of registrationt: Amtsgericht KölnNumber in associatiion registry: VR16683Umsatzsteuer-Identifikationsnummer: DE269672089
Represented by the Board in terms of §26 BGB (German Civil Code). :
Laurence A. Bannerman, President
Michael Kesseler, Vice President
Nigel Williams, Vice President
Responsible for the Content according to § 55 Abs. 2 RStV: Elisabeth Herles, General Secretary, contact see above
Website Disclaimer(1) Introduction - This disclaimer governs your use of our website; by using our website, you accept this disclaimer in full. If you disagree with any part of this disclaimer, do not use our website.(2) Intellectual Property Rights - Unless otherwise stated, we or our licensors own the intellectual property rights in the website and material on the website. Subject to the licence below, all our intellectual property rights are reserved.(3) Licence to Use Website - You may view, download for caching purposes only, and print pages from the website, provided that:(a) You must not republish material from this website (including republication on another website), or reproduce or store material from this website in any public or private electronic retrieval system. (Though we encourage fair use for academic / non commercial purposes)(b) You must not reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, resell, visit, or otherwise exploit our website or material on our website for a commercial purpose, without our express written consent;(4) Limitations of Liability - The information on this website is provided free-of-charge, and you acknowledge that it would be unreasonable to hold us liable in respect of this website and the information on this website.Whilst we endeavour to ensure that the information on this website is correct, we do not warrant its completeness or accuracy; nor do we not commit to ensuring that the website remains available or that the material on this website is kept up-to-date.To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law we exclude all representations, warranties and conditions (including, without limitation, the conditions implied by law of satisfactory quality, fitness for purpose and the use of reasonable care and skill).Our liability is limited and excluded to the maximum extent permitted under applicable law. We will not be liable for any direct, indirect or consequential loss or damage arising under this disclaimer or in connection with our website, whether arising in tort, contract, or otherwise - including, without limitation, any loss of profit, contracts, business, goodwill, data, income, revenue or anticipated savings.However, nothing in this disclaimer shall exclude or limit our liability for fraud, for death or personal injury caused by our negligence, or for any other liability which cannot be excluded or limited under applicable law.(5) Third party websitesThe website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content of third party websites.(6) Variation - We may revise this disclaimer from time-to-time. Please check this page regularly to ensure you are familiar with the current version.(7) Entire agreement - This disclaimer constitutes the entire agreement between you and us in relation to your use of our website, and supersedes all previous agreements in respect of your use of this website.(8) Law and Jurisdiction - This notice will be governed by and construed in accordance with German and European law, and any disputes relating to this notice shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Germany.(9) Our Contact Details -See Imprint above or you can contact us through our contact page.Website Privacy PolicyWe do not actually collect any information from our users other than the standard information that our website statistics automatically gathers (Google Analytics). The following is just a standard Privacy Policy agreement (we do respect people's privacy!).--------------------------We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.(1) What information do we collect?We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:(a) information about your visits to and use of this website;(b) information about any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services;(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us and/or subscribing to our website services and/or email notifications.(2) Information about website visitsWe may collect information about you computer and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views. We may use this information in the administration of this website, to improve the website's usability, and for marketing purposes.We use cookies on this website. A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.We may send a cookie which may be stored on by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We may use the information we obtain from the cookie in the administration of this website, to improve the website's usability and for marketing purposes. We may also use that information to recognise your computer when you visit our website, and to personalise our website for you. Our advertisers may also send you cookies.Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookie by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.(3) Using your personal dataPersonal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may use your personal information to:(a) improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;(b) send information (other than marketing communications) to you which we think may be of interest to you by post or by email or similar technology;(c) send to you marketing communications relating to our business [or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties] which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications to be sent by Emailing us.(d) provide other companies with statistical information about our users - but this information will not be used to identify any individual user. We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.(4) Other disclosuresIn addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you:(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and(d) to the purchaser or seller (or prospective purchaser or seller) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling or purchasing.Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.(5) International data transfersInformation that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.(6) Security of your personal dataWe will take reasonable precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.(7) Policy amendmentsWe may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.(8) Third party websitesThe website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies (or content) of third party websites.(9) Contact - You can contact us through our contact page
Imprint & Privacy & Disclaimer
© 2015 - 2020 EPA. All rights reserved. By We Focus
